

# MAICON JUNIO HEREDES LOPES

FRONT END DEVELOPER

## PROFILE

I'm a developer with 6 years of experience, 3 years as a front end, which have worked in fields like content industry, government environment and business environment. Currently, I'm looking for opportunities to work remotely for companies abroad as a frontend developer.

## SKILLS

REACTJS (2 years) | VUEJS (1 year) |

JAVASCRIPT (4 years) | TYPESCRIPT (1 year) |

PHP (4 years) | SYMFONY (3 years) |

HTML (5 years) | CSS (5 years) |

MYSQL (2 years) | DOCTRINE (2 years) |

SASS (3 years)

# **EDUCATION**

University Center UNA Bachelor in Informations Systems

- Coursed between august/2014 and august/2018
- Course focus in management and development of web applications

## LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - ADVANCED PORTUGUESE - NATIVE SPANISH - BASIC

## CONTACT

Phone: +55 31 993443530 (whatsapp)

Email: maiconjunioheredeslopes130696@gmail.com

Address: Ribeirão das Neves / MG - Brazil LinkedIn: @maicon-junio-heredes-lopes

## **EXPERIENCE**

Front End Developer Hotmart March 2021 - Currently

- Enhancement and maintenance on microfrontends using ReactJS and VueJS frameworks
- Optimizing javascript methods to improve the performance
- Converting javascript components to use typescript

Front End Developer Stefanini November 2019 - March 2021

- Maintenance on government platform using html5, css3, javascript, jquery and java jsp
- Creating a SPA platform using ReactJS and him features like redux, styled components, hooks and ci/cd
- Experience working with financial government solving problems

Full Stack Developer iZap Softworks February 2016 - November 2019

- Development of websites based on photoshop layouts using html5, css3, jquery and sass
- Development of softwares on demand using php, symfony, mysql, doctrine, jquery, html5, css3 and
- Maintenance on AWS EC2 machines using ssh access and linux commands